400,000+ happy customers

PRE-BLACK FRIDAY SALE: Buy one Sleep Pod, get another 50% OFF!

[](javascript:void(0);)

### BEST SELLERS

[

389 reviews

### Kids - Hooded Sleep Pod Move

Regular price $74.99

Regular price ~$99.99~ Sale price $74.99

Unit price /  per](https://hugsleep.com/products/kids-hooded-sleep-pod-move) 

[

389 reviews

### Sleep Pod Move

Regular price $79.99

Regular price ~$99.99~ Sale price $79.99

Unit price /  per](https://hugsleep.com/products/sleep-pod-move-adult) 

[

389 reviews

### Hooded Sleep Pod Move

Regular price $89.99

Regular price ~$129.99~ Sale price $89.99

Unit price /  per](https://hugsleep.com/products/sleep-pod-move-hood) 

* [Adults Collection
    
    Featuring 100% HugStretch™ Technology](#)

BACK

* [
    
    Hooded Sleep Pod Move](https://hugsleep.com/products/sleep-pod-move-hood)
* [
    
    Sleep Pod Move Most Popular](https://hugsleep.com/products/sleep-pod-move-adult)
* [
    
    Sleep Pod Mini New](https://hugsleep.com/products/sleep-pod-mini)
* [
    
    Hug Wrap™](https://hugsleep.com/products/hug-sleep-wrap)
* [
    
    Sleep Pod](https://hugsleep.com/products/sleep-pod)

* [Kids Collection
    
    Providing comfort and inducing relaxation](#)

BACK

* [
    
    Kids - Hooded Sleep Pod New](https://hugsleep.com/products/kids-hooded-sleep-pod-move)
* [
    
    Kids Sleep Pod Mini New](https://hugsleep.com/products/kids-sleep-pod-mini)
* [
    
    Kids Hug Wrap™ New](https://hugsleep.com/products/kids-hug-wrap%E2%84%A2)
* [
    
    Elf Sleep Pod](https://hugsleep.com/products/elf-sleep-pod)

* [Pillows
    
    Comfortable body pillows for sleep support](#)

BACK

* [
    
    Hug Body Pillow™](https://hugsleep.com/products/hug-body-pillow)
* [
    
    Pod Pillow™](https://hugsleep.com/products/pod-pillow)
* [
    
    Hug Body Pillowcase](https://hugsleep.com/products/body-pillow-cases)
* [
    
    Pod Pillowcases](https://hugsleep.com/products/pillow-case)

* [Hug Accessories
    
    Sleep’s best sidekicks](#)

BACK

* [
    
    Hug Sleep Mask](https://hugsleep.com/products/hug-sleep-mask)
* [
    
    HugStretch™ Cozy Carry Bag](https://hugsleep.com/products/hugstretch%E2%84%A2-cozy-carry-bag)
* [
    
    Elf Sleep Pod](https://hugsleep.com/products/elf-sleep-pod)

* [Bundle Sales
    
    UP TO 50% OFF
    
    Bundle & Save Up to 50%](#)

BACK

* [
    
    Hooded Sleep Pod Bundle](https://hugsleep.com/products/hooded-sleep-pod-move-bundle)
* [
    
    Sleep Pod Move Bundle](https://hugsleep.com/products/sleep-pod-move-bundle)
* [
    
    Kids Hooded Sleep Pod Bundle](https://hugsleep.com/products/kids-hooded-sleep-pod-bundle-1)
* [
    
    Kids Sleep Pod Bundle](https://hugsleep.com/products/kids-sleep-pod-bundle-pair)
* [
    
    Sleep Pod Move Bundle - Turquoise](https://hugsleep.com/products/sleep-pod-pair-bundle)
* [
    
    Sleep Pod Move Bundle - Graphite](https://hugsleep.com/products/graphite-sleep-pod-bundle)
* [
    
    Hooded Sleep Pod Bundle - Graphite](https://hugsleep.com/products/graphite-hooded-sleep-pod-bundle)
* [
    
    Hooded Sleep Pod Bundle - Turquoise](https://hugsleep.com/products/hooded-sleep-pod-pair-bundle)
* [
    
    Pod Pillow™ Bundle](https://hugsleep.com/products/pod-pillow%E2%84%A2-bundle)
* [
    
    Hug Body Pillow™ Bundle](https://hugsleep.com/products/hug-body-pillow%E2%84%A2-bundle)

* [Loungewear Collection
    
    Premium hoodies and joggers](#)

BACK

* [
    
    Women’s Hoodies](https://hugsleep.com/products/women-s-hoodie-black)
* [
    
    Women’s Joggers](https://hugsleep.com/products/women-s-jogger-black)
* [
    
    Men’s Hoodies](https://hugsleep.com/products/men-s-hoodie-black)
* [
    
    Men’s Joggers](https://hugsleep.com/products/men-s-jogger-black)

“Hug Sleep is amazing. It’s like a cozy cocoon that hugs me and helps me sleep better. I love it.”

30 Night Money Back Guarantee

 Search [](https://hugsleep.com/)

* [Bundle Sale
    
    UP TO 50% OFF](https://hugsleep.com/collections/bundle-sales)

[Cart

0 items](https://hugsleep.com/cart)

Item added to your cart
-----------------------

Check out

Continue shopping

400,000+ happy customers

Shopping Cart

Your Cart is Empty!

Subtotal

[View Cart](https://hugsleep.com/cart) Checkout

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Statement
-----------------

Section 1 - What Do We De with your Information?
------------------------------------------------

When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.

When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.

Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

Section 2 - consent
-------------------

### How do you get my consent?

When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

### How do I withdraw my consent?

If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at Support@hugsleep.com

Section 3 - Disclosure
----------------------

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

Section 4 - Shopify
-------------------

Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.

Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

### Payment

If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover.

PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service ([https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms](https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms)) or Privacy Statement ([https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy)).

Section 5 - Third-Party Services
--------------------------------

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.

For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.

As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.

Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

### Links

When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

Section 6 - Security
--------------------

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

Section 7 - Cookies
-------------------

Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

\_session\_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

\_shopify\_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits

\_shopify\_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

\_secure\_session\_id, unique token, sessional

storefront\_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

Section 8 - Age of consent
--------------------------

By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

Section 9 - Changes to this Privacy policy
------------------------------------------

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

Questions and Contact Information
---------------------------------

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at [Support@Hugsleep.com](mailto:Support@Hugsleep.com).

Personal Information that we collect will be determined by your interaction with Hug Sleep, our merchants, partners, and other sources.  Here are the categories of Personal Information that we may collect when you use our Services 

_\- Identifiers,_ such as first and last name, address, phone number, email, IP address, Device Information, information collected from cookies or similar technologies.

\- I_nformation you provide when you contact us,_ such as your responses to surveys, information you provide when you contact our customer support teams, recorded conversations with our customer service, chat conversations with us, email correspondence with us, or information about others if you choose to share it with us. Chat on our site may be recorded.

This website uses cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping cart including when you have abandoned your cart and this information is used to determine when to send cart reminder messages via SMS."

Join Our Newsletter
-------------------

Stay up to date with the latest Hug Sleep offers and product availability!

  Subscribe

© 2024, [Hug Sleep Inc.](https://hugsleep.com/)

Hug Sleep Inc. products are protected by Pat.: 10,463,179, 10,842,202 & 11,116,338 and other protections

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
